It is about time I gave an answer to a question I have been asked a hundred times.
是时候回答一个被提及多次的问题了：
Where is the brand Polestar heading?
Polestar品牌将何去何从
We brought the Polestar 1 into production and we launched the Polestar 2.
我们将Polestar1投入量产，并发布了Polestar2
Now for us inside Polestar we have a clear vision of where we are going.
现在，我们对Polestar的前景有了清晰的认知
The answer is the Polestar Precept.
答案就是Polestar Precept(概念车)
Precept is an incarnation of the philosophy of our design, of our idea about how sustainability
Precept是我们设计哲学的化身
can become a driving force, a driving  energy for our new cars.
代表我们使用可持续能源作为汽车动力的理念
That is what Precept is all about.
这就是Precept概念车的意义
A big focus, a strong focus is obviously an interior, that reduces the amount of plastic that you use.
内饰显然是理念的重点之一，着眼于减少塑料的使用。
We work together with specialised partners and experts to cut the plastic content and
我们与专业公司和专家协作，在概念车的内饰中降低塑料的用量
lessen waste materials with innovative natural and recycled source materials, in the interior of the Polestar Precept.
通过创新的自然材料以及可回收材料来减少物料的浪费
With the amazing powerRibs and ampliTex technologies from our partner Bcomp,
得益于合作伙伴Bcomp公司的powerRibs(天然纤维增强)和ampliTex(天然纤维织物)技术
we turn natural fibers into lightweight and sustainable interior panels.
我们将天然纤维加入到轻量化且可回收的内饰板中
This natural composite utilises flax
这是一种亚麻天然合成材料
and these new innovative interior panels then are up to 50% lighter and they reduce the plastic content by 80% compared to the traditional ones.
这些创新的内饰板相较传统材料，最多可以减重50%，且减少了80%的塑料使用量
It’s really amazing, it’s lighter and at the same time stronger.
这种卓越的材料在减重的同时还能保持相同的强度
Now on the seats we introduce 3D Knit material,
座椅则使用了3D Knit材料
like what is used in the fashion or footwear industries.
这种材料也被用于时装和制鞋工业
It’s made out of 100% recycled yarn derived from PET, pet bottles.
完全使用可回收的涤纶丝制成，和宝特瓶的材料一样。
It’s made exactly to size with no offcuts
它可以制成各种想要的形状，避免产生边角料
and that means we’ve completely removed the waste in its production process.
这意味着我们可以完全消除生产过程中的原材料浪费
So, to show that car interior can be the nice atmosphere that you want it to be,
创造称心如意的内饰氛围
without the usual use of an excessive amount of virgin plastic,
而不像过去那样过度使用纯塑料材质，
I think that is one of the main focus areas of Precept.
我认为这就是Precept的一个主要理念
When we presented last year the Polestar 2
去年发布Polestar2时，
we were the first car brand coming out with a production car that has Android.
我们是第一个在量产车上使用安卓系统的品牌
Now that has incredible potential for the future,
它的未来不可限量
and some of it gives a glimpse of how great the system will evolve over time.
其中一些特性让我们窥见这套系统将来的演进方向
We take here in the Polestar Precept,
我们也把这套系统带到了Precept上
example given, one that I actually like the most, is the proximity sensor that we built in there.
举例来说，我最喜欢的一个特性，就是内置的距离传感器
You see an uncluttered, very easy to read aesthetically nice screen.
车内有简洁优雅的屏幕
But then when you reach out, buttons pop out, and more information comes.
当你伸出手时，按钮会弹出，同时屏幕显示更多内容
Big buttons that are easy to touch even when the car is moving.
大尺寸的按钮在行驶时更易操作
So this animated proximity sensor is really a big big step into this hassle-free future that we promise with our cars.
基于距离传感器的动画效果正是我们所承诺的简化操作的重要一环
A big leap for safety in the car is the eye tracking system of the Precept.
车辆安全性的飞跃则来自Precept的眼球追踪系统
One of the core benefits is monitoring the driver's health status.
系统的一个核心功能就是监测驾驶者的健康状况
Is he tired, is she watching the road?
他是否疲劳？她是否在看路面？
If not, the car takes appropriate actions such as warning or speed reduction.
如果有异常，车辆会做出合适的反馈，例如警示或减速
On the driver-dedicated monitor in front of you,
驾驶员前方的显示器
the information and signals of the pilot assist system are now combined with Google maps data.
展示的信息和驾驶辅助系统指示，现已与谷歌地图数据结合到了一起
So the turn-by-turn guidance is embedded into a fully contextualised navigation.
因此细致的导航指示得以嵌入到导航系统中
Where black holes for air intakes and cooling define the era of combustion engines,
传统燃油时代车型的前脸中冷进气格栅位置，
the face of the Polestar is characterised and defined by the SmartZone
在Polestar上被替换成了独特的SmartZone
where technology for safety sensors and pilot assistance is purposefully gathered.
安全传感器和驾驶辅助系统就集成在此。
Instead of tradition and preindustrial craftsmanship, we defined the new premium,
区别于传统的手工技艺，我们定义了一种新的高级感
a premium that left the convention of  leather, wood and chrome behind.
一种抛弃传统的皮革、木材、镀铬所营造的高级感
This will be the aesthetics of the electric age, high-tech minimalism that redefines
这将成为电动时代的美学，一种高科技的简约风格，
luxury for the sustainable decade.
可以重新定义下一个十年的豪华风格
*We have pressing questions that need answers.
我们已经提出了那些迫在眉睫的问题
Clearly sustainability is not limited to the electric drivetrain.
显然，可持续概念不仅仅局限于电力驱动系统
Sustainability means on a much broader sense, from the very first step of the production of the car,
可持续概念有着更加广泛的意义
to the very end when you actually take care of what is left of the car in the recycling process, to come to a fully sustainable chain of mobility.
从回收处理报废车辆的材料，到移动出行全环节的可持续链条
It’s a new era that has started
未来已至
and the Polestar Precept is a messenger of what is to come,
Polestar Precept就是新纪元的信使
and a reminder that our journey has just begun.
预示着全新的旅程才刚刚开始